- [Josh] Terraform is a powerful tool for defining,
deploying, and managing cloud infrastructure.
In this course, we'll focus on hands-on work,
spinning up resources in Amazon AWS,
and iterating on our code as we go.
By the end, we'll have built
a fully-functional Terraform module
without glossing over any steps in the process,
and we'll use it to deploy
multiple infrastructure environments.
My name is Josh Samuelson.
I'm a lead software engineer at Dropbox.
Terraform is a big part of my work,
and it has transformed my approach
to working with the cloud.
I'm excited for you to experience that same transformation,
so let's get started.